All right, Conor, now come on to the cast.
好了，Conor，接下来切到解说席。
Let's get this grand final going.
让我们正式开始这场总决赛。
We've got Na'Vi and Vitality.
对阵双方是 Na'Vi 和 Vitality。
It's a rematch.
这是一场复仇战。
And Na'Vi are back for blood.
而 Na'Vi 这次就是来复仇的。
the first test is for makazze, brought up on the desk,
第一个考验来到了makazze
he has to pass this.
他必须得先过这一关。
Guarding outside, going one for one,
外场防守先打成一换一，
might be enough.
这也许已经够了。
Plenty of information, but instantly flameZ appears.
信息已经拿满了，但 flameZ 瞬间现身。
Bit of a reset on the situation.
局势稍微缓了一下。
They now can't see the cross, and flameZ,
现在他们已经看不到过点了，而 flameZ
he's making some noise outside.
还在外场故意制造动静。
iM walks into this, but he's fine.
iM 直接走进来了，但他处理得很稳。
So clean.
太干净了。
So clean, clinical triple tap out of that one.
太干净了，这波冷静利落地连收三人。
flameZ, what recovery can you make?
flameZ，你还能怎么补救？
I bet absolutely nothing.
我看基本没戏了。
Minute on the clock.
时间还剩一分钟。
Bomb on the opposite side of the map here, Mohan.
炸弹可还在地图另一头呢，Mohan。
That is the kind
这就是那种
of clinical precision
极度冷静、极度精准的处理，
that we're gonna need from somebody out of Na'Vi
今晚 Na'Vi 必须得有人打出这种表现
at the get-go.
从开局就得站出来。
Like Mauisnake said, even when it's B1ad3, maybe,
就像 Mauisnake 说的，哪怕是 B1ad3 也好，
taking timeouts a little too late,
有时候暂停都叫得稍微晚了一点，
whatever it needs to be,
不管问题到底出在哪，
it's gotta start well for Na'Vi tonight.
今晚 Na'Vi 都必须先把开局打好。
Yep, I was looking back at this core. Oh, okay.
对，我刚刚还在回看这套核心数据。哦，等等。
Wait a second, he's got that second headshot,
等一下，他连第二个爆头都拿到了，
meant to be impossible.
这本来几乎是不可能的。
Two players on top of that bomb had possession.
当时可是有两个人已经踩住了包点位置。
He catches them in transition.
结果他正好抓到对手转移的瞬间。
He teases them with the feet on the ladder.
他在梯子上露脚，故意把对面钓出来。
This is interesting, actually.
这下其实有点意思了。
Aleksib's got a smoke to work with.
Aleksib 手里还有一颗烟。
flameZ has 11 HP.
flameZ 只剩 11 点血。
But we're talking about pistol round.
但别忘了，这可是手枪局。
P250 comes out.
P250 掏出来了。
One headshot makes the difference. Let's see.
只要一个爆头就能改写结局，看看吧。
Wow, that was close.
哇，这也太接近了。
Very nice round out of b1t, obviously.
这回合 b1t 打得确实漂亮。